Unload the cargo.
Heard the goods are pretty good today.
The goods are here.
What beautiful eyes.
What are you waiting for.
Don't waste her.
This chick's kind of interesting.
Rest assured I'll sell you a good price.
Fuck.
True top.
You.
Who are you guys.
Old Man's men.
Thank you for saving us.
You're welcome.
Thanks.
Time to clean up the trash.
What are you doing.
Cleaning up the trash.
Bodies.
Weapons.
And these little scraps.
Blow 'em all up.
Old Man's rule: Leave no loose ends.
A bunch of kids—what threat are they.
Being alive is a threat.
If other traffickers catch 'em.
Their fate'll be even worse.
Better to die quick. Than live in pain.
Touch bomb—one touch and it blows.
Break Old Man's rules, and we all die.
Cut the crap.
We're running out of time.
Have fun by yourself.
Get back.
This shop.
Only the blind girl and her sister run it.
What are you doing.
What's going on sister.
Easy, easy, don't panic.
We brothers.
Starting on the first of this month.
We're here to collect protection money.
Not much.
Fifty grand.
Okay I'll pay you.
Let's talk outside.
That easy.
Should I ask for interest, then.
Let go of me.
Never tried a blind girl before.
Hi, Sister.
Come here.
Hello.
This is 911.
How may I help you.
We've located your phone.
Please keep the line open.
I'll fucking kill you.
Badge number 9501.
A murder case occurred on Nanyang Street.
Request support.
Sister.
Are you okay.
It's okay.
Don't be afraid.
Those were just standard procedures.
That's why it was formal.
No need to be nervous.
The major Nancheng train accident three years ago you two were on that train.
Yes.
My sister saved thirteen people in the carriage.
Many reporters wanted to interview her.
But she refused all of them.
Fame is a good thing. Why refuse.
It was just a disaster.
Nothing to brag about.
Help.
Mingzhu, don't be afraid.
Sister.
Is it you.
A blessing in disguise.
Heaven let me meet my sister in that accident.
If not for my sister I can't go to a school for the blind either.
Did you open the coffee shop together.
Yeah.
You can too.
My sister puts things in fixed places
I know where they are by touch.
Sir.
Confirmed.
The one who escaped is Poison Rat
I think we can issue a warrant immediately.
Without solid evidence don't alert the enemy.
Sir...
Can we leave now.
Yes.
Keep your phone on.
Sister, are you hurt.
I'm fine.
But.
Why are you home so early today.
I wanted to surprise you
I didn't expect this to happen.
Luckily the police came in time.
But.
Next time you come home.
Tell me in advance.
Got it.
Mingzhu.
There's a little beggar behind us.
Wait here for a moment I'll go give him some change.
Wait here for me.
Bold move.
Let's talk over there.
Nice spot you picked.
I picked it just for you.
Tell my brothers what you have to say.
Sister.
I'm here.
I have change too.
He's already gone.
Let's go home.
Mingzhu.
Go to Aunt Chen's and buy me some guangbing
I have to clean the equipment tonight.
You finally let me go out alone
I'm leaving then.
Be careful.
Okay.
I suspect this isn't a simple disappearance.
Poison Rat knows too much.
This case could be a breakthrough.
To crack the cross-border crime syndicate.
We're not the only ones looking for him.
Several other forces have their eyes on him.
Insufficient evidence.
Clues are lost.
Further investigation is a waste of resources.
Close the case.
Close it.
If we let this clue go we'll never get close again.
You're a cop.
You must follow orders.
If we don't investigate, who will.
I don't want you to end up like your father.
He threw himself into cases and lost his life.
You're still young.
I won't sign the closure report.
By ten tomorrow morning I want the case files on my desk.
There have been multiple homicides in the city recently.
Police suspect a professional assassin organization is behind these murders.
The organization uses cruel methods.
Leaving no survivors.
They're also suspected of. Colluding with local criminal gangs to carry out targeted assassinations.
Hello.
Check the surveillance near the coffee shop again for me.
Any leads on Poison Rat.
Beautiful, kind lovely and excellent Ms. Minghui.
Your delivery has arrived safely.
You're back.
Let's have dinner first.
It smells good.
If you don't come eat your guangbing will be in Mingzhu's belly.
I'm still cleaning the equipment, Mingzhu
I'll bring it down to you.
Don't come down.
The floor is slippery.
It's okay
I'll wait here for you.
Sister.
Do you remember. When we were at the orphanage
I was always hungry.
Every time my stomach growled you'd always magically get me guangbing.
Back then, I really thought guangbing was the most delicious thing in the world.
Mingzhu, here's your guangbing.
Eat slowly, don't choke.
Sister.
You eat too.
I'm full.
You eat.
Later I found out.
Those flatbreads who got these back every time you got beaten.
Sister.
Are you listening.
I'm listening.
After you left my birthday wish every year was for you to come back.
Today is the third anniversary of our reunion.
Sister.
We'll never be apart again.
Right.
Yes.
Never again.
Sister.
All these years were you alone too.
Someone adopted me and some other kids.
We called him Old Man.
Stay in formation.
Hang onto the rope.
Check your weapons.
Then push forward with force.
Ladies.
Stay low in the water, goddammit.
Keep your heads down.
Good, good.
Pull harder.
Close combat, yes, good.
Excellent.
Our goal is to become.
The deadliest weapons in the world.
The most elite and capable.
This is the only way we survive in this damn world.
Understand.
Yes, Old Man.
What are we.
Family.
What must you always remember.
Never part.
Don't go soft just because she's your sister.
This is your killer instinct
children.
Today.
It is to help you learn.
In no circumstances can we relax our vigilance.
I want to see you all. How to Turn the Tables in Adversity.
Go back.
Hold her down.
Tide.
You are excellent.
But you need to learn to solve problems on your own.
You are now protecting her.
It's also destroying oneself.
Lock her up.
Eat quickly.
Slow down.
Thank you.
Have you ever thought about leaving here.
Yes.
But I have to survive first.
Where will you go when you leave.
Find my sister.
She's blind.
I'm very worried about her.
What about you.
Me I don't know.
Where's your family.
Then from now on
I'll be your sister.
We grew up together.
No one was ever left behind.
After you came back do you still keep in touch with them.
No.
We went our separate ways after we grew up.
If he saw how happy I am he'd be happy for me.
Sister.
All these years have you been through a lot alone.
As long as you're by my side everything is worth it.
Class dismissed.
Slow down.
The legislators are very satisfied with you.
These campaign obstacles were all handled very smoothly.
But there's one loose end.
There was a person named Tooru-ji.
Know a lot of things about us.
He caused trouble and disappeared.
If Someone else finds him it'll be bad for us.
Dig him out for me.
Where was he last seen.
Your coffee is ready.
Thank you.
You waited for me so late
I'm leaving now.
Bye.
Bye, take care.
Sorry, we're closed.
Hello.
Are you alone here.
My sister is here too.
She'll be back soon.
Can I help you with something.
Looking for someone.
Who.
The person in this photo.
Is this your sister.
Yes.
What's her name.
Minghui.
Do you know her.
We're good friends who grew up together.
We know each other very well.
Good friends.
I know about you two.
My sister told me.
What did she say.
She said even though you're both orphans.
But helped each other.
You're very close.
We Are indeed very close.
She helped me a lot.
Long time no see.
Minghui.
Sister, look who's here.
Mingzhu.
Go pour two drinks.
Okay.
Sit.
You're actually alive.
Playing house fun.
How did you find this place.
Looking for someone.
Named Poison Rat.
Since he's on your turf.
I assume you've taken care of him
I've heard you're the best.
I'd really like to play with you.
This is my new recruit.
Named Torpedo.
Drinks are here.
Little sister.
Let me help you.
Thank you.
Thanks.
Good job.
What a coincidence
I didn't expect to meet my sister's friend here.
Me neither.
But Minghui's best friend isn't me.
It's someone named.
Tide girl.
Tide.
Tide is dead.
Yeah.
Before coming here I also thought the tide was dead.
But I just found out she's alive.
It's late.
Let's talk tomorrow. Why the rush.
You haven't finished your drink.
Next time.
Now's fine.
Sister.
Sister Little blind girl.
Did you really think she was your sister.
Mingzhu.
Sister.
Run.
Save her.
I can't take this job.
She's my sister.
Then take her to the hospital.
Save her.
She needs a blood transfusion.
Take mine.
So the tides disguise themselves as Minghui.
Beside Minghui's own younger sister.
Play house.
Yes.
Interesting.
Let's go check over there.
Don't worry
I snuck out too.
What do you want.
Take me with you.
Hiding in the cave for two days.
You thought we couldn't find you.
What are you doing.
Running away from home.
Why are you two running.
Old Man.
They don't really want to leave.
You raised us all.
We… we won't leave.
We won't leave.
Good kids.
What are the family rules.
Leaving means betrayal.
Betrayal has a price.
You are her sister.
The family rules.
You carry it out.
Do it.
No! Sister, don't.
Sister.
No, no.
No, no. I can't.
Old Man, I can't do it.
Shoot.
Sister, don't
I can't do it.
Tide.
Your turn.
Minghui.
You carry it out.
Mingzhu.
My sister's blood type doesn't match mine.
Who are you, really.
Let's recover first, okay.
I need two identities.
You took a bullet for her.
Bled for her.
Was it worth it.
What about you.
At first, I followed Old Man down this path
thinking I was upholding justice.
In the end, I realized I was just a fool being played by others.
Old Man and I founded this organization because we found you.
We wanted to eliminate evil.
I was quick.
They didn't make a sound when they died.
It shouldn't have been that painful.
I'm gonna kill you.
Unexpectedly.
In the end I was still counterattacked by evil.
Turning us into evil itself.
I've done too many wrong things.
I need to atone.
This is the last place Poison Rat might appear.
But there are no cameras in this alley.
Only this dashcam.
Sister.
Sister. Where on earth are you.
Little girl, what's wrong.
Do you need help.
I I I need to go to the police station.
You can go ahead.
We're at the police station.
How can I help you.
I I'm looking for my sister.
Come in with me.
Come on, slow down.
Don't be afraid.
Sit there for a moment
I'll get you a glass of water.
Don't be afraid.
Where is she.
Don't worry, little girl.
I already called your sister.
She'll come pick you up soon.
No.
No, sir.
That woman isn't my sister.
I don't know who my real sister is.
I'll tell you. Who your sister is.
Who are you.
Little blind girl.
It's you.
Who are you people.
Master
I found a new clue.
Officer Zhiming.
Help me.
They're bad people.
Nonsense.
Zhiming, Chunjiao.
You two, get out.
Get out
clear the area.
Hey.
That loser leave him to me.
He's caused me nothing but trouble all these years
I'll make him suffer.
You bastard.
Good luck to you.
Minghui.
I'm here to pick up my sister.
As soon as I got to the station I found your siste delirious in the office.
She kept calling for her sister.
So I called you.
With her mental state right now you really need to keep an eye on her.
Or she could get hurt.
Don't… don't kill me.
Where is Mingzhu
I'll take you to her
've taken good care of your sister.
Cut the crap.
Do it.
Why are you hesitating.
Where is Mingzhu.
Chunjiao.
As expected of you.
I miss you, kid.
Let her go.
What will you trade for her.
She's useless to me.
Let her go
I'll do anything you say.
Take her down.
Please.
Stop fighting.
Let her go.
She's not even your sister.
Do you know her past. How much blood is on her hands.
Stop talking.
You're not like the thing I raised.
Your sister is dead.
Stop it.
She's the one who killed your sister.
Old Man.
I'm begging you.
The gun.
Load it.
Put your hand here.
Aim... aim.
Aim.
I'm sorry, Child.
Time is running out, child
Cherish my last lesson.
Leaving means betrayal.
Betrayal has a price.
Close your eyes, my child.
It'll be over soon.
You.
Old Man.
Never part.
Mingzhu.
Don't be afraid.
I'm here.
What he just said is it true.
Tide.
Your turn.
Old Man.
If you let Tide go.
I'll do anything.
Old Man.
I'm begging you, Old Man.
What do I have to do
for you to let Tide go.
I'm begging you.
Please, please.
You talk too much.
If you'll let Tide go.
I'll never speak again.
Congratulations.
You get to live now.
But she's useless now.
Minghui died for me.
But from that day on.
I never truly lived again.
Until I found you.
I found a reason to live.
If none of this had happened would you have told me the truth.
I hope you'll always stay kind.
Live happily every day.
I let you live not to send you to hell but to live like a human being.
Minghui is my sister.
So are you.
You both are.
My family.
Sister.
What's wrong, Sister.
Mingzhu.
Officer Zhiming.
Hurry.
Take my sister to the hospital.
Officer Zhiming.
Please drive faster.
Hold on a little longer.
We're almost there.
Don't sleep, Sister.
Hold on, hold on.
The car broke down
I'll check.
Sister.
Hold on, Sister.
There has to be a way.
This is as far as we go